{"QandA":

[
 {
   "ID": 1,
   "Question": "Capital city of Afghanistan?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Kabul",
   "Answer1": "Abu Dhabi",
   "Answer2": "Kabul",
   "Answer3": "Pristina"
 },
 {
   "ID": 2,
   "Question": "Capital city of Albania?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Tirana",
   "Answer1": "Tirana",
   "Answer2": "Yamoussoukro",
   "Answer3": "Abuja"
 },
 {
   "ID": 3,
   "Question": "Capital city of Algeria?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Algiers",
   "Answer1": "Accra",
   "Answer2": "Algiers",
   "Answer3": "Cairo"
 },
 {
   "ID": 4,
   "Question": "Capital city of Andorra?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Andorra la Vella",
   "Answer1": "Andorra la Vella",
   "Answer2": "Apia",
   "Answer3": "Addis Ababa"
 },
 {
   "ID": 5,
   "Question": "Capital city of Angola?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Luanda",
   "Answer1": "Budapest",
   "Answer2": "Luanda",
   "Answer3": "Algiers"
 },
 {
   "ID": 6,
   "Question": "Capital city of Antigua and Barbuda?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Saint John's",
   "Answer1": "Saint John's",
   "Answer2": "Amman",
   "Answer3": "Ngerulmud"
 },
 {
   "ID": 7,
   "Question": "Capital city of Argentina?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Buenos Aires",
   "Answer1": "Amsterdam",
   "Answer2": "Tegucigalpa",
   "Answer3": "Buenos Aires"
 },
 {
   "ID": 8,
   "Question": "Capital city of Armenia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Yerevan",
   "Answer1": "Yerevan",
   "Answer2": "Yaounde",
   "Answer3": "Andorra la Vella"
 },
 {
   "ID": 9,
   "Question": "Capital city of Australia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Canberra",
   "Answer1": "Ankara",
   "Answer2": "Moroni",
   "Answer3": "Canberra"
 },
 {
   "ID": 10,
   "Question": "Capital city of Austria?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Vienna",
   "Answer1": "Guatemala City",
   "Answer2": "Vienna",
   "Answer3": "Antananarivo"
 },
 {
   "ID": 11,
   "Question": "Capital city of Azerbaijan?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Baku",
   "Answer1": "Baku",
   "Answer2": "Apia",
   "Answer3": "Vilnius"
 },
 {
   "ID": 12,
   "Question": "Capital city of Bahamas?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Nassau",
   "Answer1": "Ashgabat",
   "Answer2": "Damascus",
   "Answer3": "Nassau"
 },
 {
   "ID": 13,
   "Question": "Capital city of Bahrain?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Manama",
   "Answer1": "Luxembourg ",
   "Answer2": "Asmara",
   "Answer3": "Manama"
 },
 {
   "ID": 14,
   "Question": "Capital city of Bangladesh?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Dhaka",
   "Answer1": "Dhaka",
   "Answer2": "Maputo",
   "Answer3": "Astana"
 },
 {
   "ID": 15,
   "Question": "Capital city of Barbados?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Bridgetown",
   "Answer1": "Bridgetown",
   "Answer2": "Antananarivo",
   "Answer3": "Asunción"
 },
 {
   "ID": 16,
   "Question": "Capital city of Belarus?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Minsk",
   "Answer1": "Athens",
   "Answer2": "Vientiane",
   "Answer3": "Minsk"
 },
 {
   "ID": 17,
   "Question": "Capital city of Belgium?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Brussels",
   "Answer1": "Brussels",
   "Answer2": "Bucharest",
   "Answer3": "Baghdad"
 },
 {
   "ID": 18,
   "Question": "Capital city of Belize?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Belmopan",
   "Answer1": "Brasilia",
   "Answer2": "Belmopan",
   "Answer3": "Baku"
 },
 {
   "ID": 19,
   "Question": "Capital city of Benin?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Porto-Novo",
   "Answer1": "Porto-Novo",
   "Answer2": "Bamako",
   "Answer3": "Nassau"
 },
 {
   "ID": 20,
   "Question": "Capital city of Bhutan?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Thimphu",
   "Answer1": "Thimphu",
   "Answer2": "Amman",
   "Answer3": "Bandar Seri Begawan"
 },
 {
   "ID": 21,
   "Question": "Capital city of Bolivia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Sucre (de jure)",
   "Answer1": "Bangkok",
   "Answer2": "Sucre (de jure)",
   "Answer3": "Ljubljana"
 },
 {
   "ID": 22,
   "Question": "Capital city of Bosnia and Herzegovina?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Sarajevo",
   "Answer1": "Banjul",
   "Answer2": "Lima",
   "Answer3": "Sarajevo"
 },
 {
   "ID": 23,
   "Question": "Capital city of Botswana?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Gaborone",
   "Answer1": "Gaborone",
   "Answer2": "Basseterre",
   "Answer3": "Vienna"
 },
 {
   "ID": 24,
   "Question": "Capital city of Brazil?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Brasilia",
   "Answer1": "Beijing",
   "Answer2": "London",
   "Answer3": "Brasilia"
 },
 {
   "ID": 25,
   "Question": "Capital city of Brunei?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Bandar Seri Begawan",
   "Answer1": "Beirut",
   "Answer2": "Nouakchott",
   "Answer3": "Bandar Seri Begawan"
 },
 {
   "ID": 26,
   "Question": "Capital city of Bulgaria?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Sofia",
   "Answer1": "Belgrade",
   "Answer2": "Bujumbura",
   "Answer3": "Sofia"
 },
 {
   "ID": 27,
   "Question": "Capital city of Burkina Faso?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Ouagadougou",
   "Answer1": "Tunis",
   "Answer2": "Belmopan",
   "Answer3": "Ouagadougou"
 },
 {
   "ID": 28,
   "Question": "Capital city of Burundi?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Bujumbura",
   "Answer1": "Kampala",
   "Answer2": "Berlin",
   "Answer3": "Bujumbura"
 },
 {
   "ID": 29,
   "Question": "Capital city of Cabo Verde?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Praia",
   "Answer1": "Bern",
   "Answer2": "Praia",
   "Answer3": "Abu Dhabi"
 },
 {
   "ID": 30,
   "Question": "Capital city of Cambodia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Phnom Penh",
   "Answer1": "Bishkek",
   "Answer2": "Phnom Penh",
   "Answer3": "Suva"
 },
 {
   "ID": 31,
   "Question": "Capital city of Cameroon?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Yaounde",
   "Answer1": "Bissau",
   "Answer2": "Yaounde",
   "Answer3": "Lomé"
 },
 {
   "ID": 32,
   "Question": "Capital city of Canada?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Ottawa",
   "Answer1": "Manila",
   "Answer2": "Bogotá",
   "Answer3": "Ottawa"
 },
 {
   "ID": 33,
   "Question": "Capital city of Central African Republic?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Bangui",
   "Answer1": "Bangui",
   "Answer2": "Brasilia",
   "Answer3": "Bogotá"
 },
 {
   "ID": 34,
   "Question": "Capital city of Chad?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "N'Djamena",
   "Answer1": "Bratislava",
   "Answer2": "N'Djamena",
   "Answer3": "Sana'a"
 },
 {
   "ID": 35,
   "Question": "Capital city of Chile?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Santiago",
   "Answer1": "Brazzaville",
   "Answer2": "Santiago",
   "Answer3": "Kabul"
 },
 {
   "ID": 36,
   "Question": "Capital city of China?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Beijing",
   "Answer1": "Beijing",
   "Answer2": "Bridgetown",
   "Answer3": "Port of Spain"
 },
 {
   "ID": 37,
   "Question": "Capital city of Colombia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Bogotá",
   "Answer1": "Brussels",
   "Answer2": "Rome",
   "Answer3": "Bogotá"
 },
 {
   "ID": 38,
   "Question": "Capital city of Comoros?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Moroni",
   "Answer1": "Bucharest",
   "Answer2": "Moroni",
   "Answer3": "Dushanbe"
 },
 {
   "ID": 39,
   "Question": "Capital city of Democratic Republic of theCongo?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Kinshasa",
   "Answer1": "Ottawa",
   "Answer2": "Kinshasa",
   "Answer3": "Budapest"
 },
 {
   "ID": 40,
   "Question": "Capital city of Republic of the Congo?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Brazzaville",
   "Answer1": "Buenos Aires",
   "Answer2": "Berlin",
   "Answer3": "Brazzaville"
 },
 {
   "ID": 41,
   "Question": "Capital city of Costa Rica?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "San Jose",
   "Answer1": "San Jose",
   "Answer2": "Bujumbura",
   "Answer3": "Wellington"
 },
 {
   "ID": 42,
   "Question": "Capital city of Cote d'Ivoire?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Yamoussoukro",
   "Answer1": "New Delhi",
   "Answer2": "Yamoussoukro",
   "Answer3": "Cairo"
 },
 {
   "ID": 43,
   "Question": "Capital city of Croatia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Zagreb",
   "Answer1": "Ankara",
   "Answer2": "Canberra",
   "Answer3": "Zagreb"
 },
 {
   "ID": 44,
   "Question": "Capital city of Cuba?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Havana",
   "Answer1": "Caracas",
   "Answer2": "Oslo",
   "Answer3": "Havana"
 },
 {
   "ID": 45,
   "Question": "Capital city of Cyprus?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Nicosia",
   "Answer1": "Jakarta",
   "Answer2": "Castries",
   "Answer3": "Nicosia"
 },
 {
   "ID": 46,
   "Question": "Capital city of Czech Republic?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Prague",
   "Answer1": "Chisinau",
   "Answer2": "Port Moresby",
   "Answer3": "Prague"
 },
 {
   "ID": 47,
   "Question": "Capital city of Denmark?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Copenhagen",
   "Answer1": "Conakry",
   "Answer2": "Juba",
   "Answer3": "Copenhagen"
 },
 {
   "ID": 48,
   "Question": "Capital city of Djibouti?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Djibouti ",
   "Answer1": "Copenhagen",
   "Answer2": "Djibouti ",
   "Answer3": "Dodoma"
 },
 {
   "ID": 49,
   "Question": "Capital city of Dominica?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Roseau",
   "Answer1": "Roseau",
   "Answer2": "Prague",
   "Answer3": "Dakar"
 },
 {
   "ID": 50,
   "Question": "Capital city of Dominican Republic?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Santo Domingo",
   "Answer1": "Doha",
   "Answer2": "Santo Domingo",
   "Answer3": "Damascus"
 },
 {
   "ID": 51,
   "Question": "Capital city of Ecuador?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Quito",
   "Answer1": "Quito",
   "Answer2": "Dhaka",
   "Answer3": "Podgorica"
 },
 {
   "ID": 52,
   "Question": "Capital city of Egypt?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Cairo",
   "Answer1": "Dili",
   "Answer2": "Cairo",
   "Answer3": "Conakry"
 },
 {
   "ID": 53,
   "Question": "Capital city of El Salvador?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "San Salvador",
   "Answer1": "Djibouti ",
   "Answer2": "San Salvador",
   "Answer3": "Windhoek"
 },
 {
   "ID": 54,
   "Question": "Capital city of Equatorial Guinea?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Malabo (de jure)",
   "Answer1": "Dodoma",
   "Answer2": "Athens",
   "Answer3": "Malabo (de jure)"
 },
 {
   "ID": 55,
   "Question": "Capital city of Eritrea?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Asmara",
   "Answer1": "Basseterre",
   "Answer2": "Asmara",
   "Answer3": "Doha"
 },
 {
   "ID": 56,
   "Question": "Capital city of Estonia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Tallinn",
   "Answer1": "Tallinn",
   "Answer2": "Dublin",
   "Answer3": "Kuwait City"
 },
 {
   "ID": 57,
   "Question": "Capital city of Ethiopia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Addis Ababa",
   "Answer1": "Dushanbe",
   "Answer2": "Maseru",
   "Answer3": "Addis Ababa"
 },
 {
   "ID": 58,
   "Question": "Capital city of Fiji?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Suva",
   "Answer1": "Suva",
   "Answer2": "Rabat",
   "Answer3": "Freetown"
 },
 {
   "ID": 59,
   "Question": "Capital city of Finland?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Helsinki",
   "Answer1": "Helsinki",
   "Answer2": "Funafuti",
   "Answer3": "Bissau"
 },
 {
   "ID": 60,
   "Question": "Capital city of France?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Paris",
   "Answer1": "Gaborone",
   "Answer2": "Paris",
   "Answer3": "Nicosia"
 },
 {
   "ID": 61,
   "Question": "Capital city of Gabon?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Libreville",
   "Answer1": "Libreville",
   "Answer2": "Freetown",
   "Answer3": "Georgetown"
 },
 {
   "ID": 62,
   "Question": "Capital city of Gambia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Banjul",
   "Answer1": "Guatemala City",
   "Answer2": "Banjul",
   "Answer3": "Kingstown"
 },
 {
   "ID": 63,
   "Question": "Capital city of Georgia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Tbilisi",
   "Answer1": "Tbilisi",
   "Answer2": "Hanoi",
   "Answer3": "Khartoum"
 },
 {
   "ID": 64,
   "Question": "Capital city of Germany?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Berlin",
   "Answer1": "Mogadishu",
   "Answer2": "Berlin",
   "Answer3": "Harare"
 },
 {
   "ID": 65,
   "Question": "Capital city of Ghana?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Accra",
   "Answer1": "Accra",
   "Answer2": "Victoria",
   "Answer3": "Havana"
 },
 {
   "ID": 66,
   "Question": "Capital city of Greece?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Athens",
   "Answer1": "Yerevan",
   "Answer2": "Helsinki",
   "Answer3": "Athens"
 },
 {
   "ID": 67,
   "Question": "Capital city of Grenada?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Saint George's",
   "Answer1": "Pyongyang",
   "Answer2": "Saint George's",
   "Answer3": "Honiara"
 },
 {
   "ID": 68,
   "Question": "Capital city of Guatemala?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Guatemala City",
   "Answer1": "Bandar Seri Begawan",
   "Answer2": "Islamabad",
   "Answer3": "Guatemala City"
 },
 {
   "ID": 69,
   "Question": "Capital city of Guinea?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Conakry",
   "Answer1": "Conakry",
   "Answer2": "Jakarta",
   "Answer3": "Copenhagen"
 },
 {
   "ID": 70,
   "Question": "Capital city of Guinea-Bissau?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Bissau",
   "Answer1": "Bissau",
   "Answer2": "Jerusalem",
   "Answer3": "Bishkek"
 },
 {
   "ID": 71,
   "Question": "Capital city of Guyana?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Georgetown",
   "Answer1": "Jerusalem (East)",
   "Answer2": "Asmara",
   "Answer3": "Georgetown"
 },
 {
   "ID": 72,
   "Question": "Capital city of Haiti?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Port-au-Prince",
   "Answer1": "Tbilisi",
   "Answer2": "Juba",
   "Answer3": "Port-au-Prince"
 },
 {
   "ID": 73,
   "Question": "Capital city of Honduras?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Tegucigalpa",
   "Answer1": "Tegucigalpa",
   "Answer2": "Vatican City",
   "Answer3": "Kabul"
 },
 {
   "ID": 74,
   "Question": "Capital city of Hungary?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Budapest",
   "Answer1": "Budapest",
   "Answer2": "Kampala",
   "Answer3": "Saint John's"
 },
 {
   "ID": 75,
   "Question": "Capital city of Iceland?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Reykjavik",
   "Answer1": "San Jose",
   "Answer2": "Kathmandu",
   "Answer3": "Reykjavik"
 },
 {
   "ID": 76,
   "Question": "Capital city of India?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "New Delhi",
   "Answer1": "New Delhi",
   "Answer2": "Ulaanbaatar",
   "Answer3": "Khartoum"
 },
 {
   "ID": 77,
   "Question": "Capital city of Indonesia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Jakarta",
   "Answer1": "Asmara",
   "Answer2": "Jakarta",
   "Answer3": "Kigali"
 },
 {
   "ID": 78,
   "Question": "Capital city of Iran?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Tehran",
   "Answer1": "Tehran",
   "Answer2": "Kingston",
   "Answer3": "Buenos Aires"
 },
 {
   "ID": 79,
   "Question": "Capital city of Iraq?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Baghdad",
   "Answer1": "Kingstown",
   "Answer2": "Baghdad",
   "Answer3": "Naypyidaw"
 },
 {
   "ID": 80,
   "Question": "Capital city of Ireland?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Dublin",
   "Answer1": "Dublin",
   "Answer2": "Muscat",
   "Answer3": "Kinshasa"
 },
 {
   "ID": 81,
   "Question": "Capital city of Israel?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Jerusalem",
   "Answer1": "Dakar",
   "Answer2": "Jerusalem",
   "Answer3": "Kuala Lumpur"
 },
 {
   "ID": 82,
   "Question": "Capital city of Italy?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Rome",
   "Answer1": "Kuwait City",
   "Answer2": "Rome",
   "Answer3": "Taipei"
 },
 {
   "ID": 83,
   "Question": "Capital city of Jamaica?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Kingston",
   "Answer1": "Kingston",
   "Answer2": "Kyiv (Kiev)",
   "Answer3": "Male"
 },
 {
   "ID": 84,
   "Question": "Capital city of Japan?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Tokyo",
   "Answer1": "Tokyo",
   "Answer2": "Baghdad",
   "Answer3": "La Paz (seat of government)"
 },
 {
   "ID": 85,
   "Question": "Capital city of Jordan?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Amman",
   "Answer1": "Libreville",
   "Answer2": "Amman",
   "Answer3": "Madrid"
 },
 {
   "ID": 86,
   "Question": "Capital city of Kazakhstan?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Astana",
   "Answer1": "Astana",
   "Answer2": "Lilongwe",
   "Answer3": "Addis Ababa"
 },
 {
   "ID": 87,
   "Question": "Capital city of Kenya?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Nairobi",
   "Answer1": "Nairobi",
   "Answer2": "Kinshasa",
   "Answer3": "Lima"
 },
 {
   "ID": 88,
   "Question": "Capital city of Kiribati?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Tarawa",
   "Answer1": "Mbabane (administrative)",
   "Answer2": "Tarawa",
   "Answer3": "Lisbon"
 },
 {
   "ID": 89,
   "Question": "Capital city of Kosovo?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Pristina",
   "Answer1": "Pristina",
   "Answer2": "Ljubljana",
   "Answer3": "Beijing"
 },
 {
   "ID": 90,
   "Question": "Capital city of Kuwait?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Kuwait City",
   "Answer1": "Kuwait City",
   "Answer2": "Belgrade",
   "Answer3": "Lomé"
 },
 {
   "ID": 91,
   "Question": "Capital city of Kyrgyzstan?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Bishkek",
   "Answer1": "São Tomé",
   "Answer2": "Bishkek",
   "Answer3": "London"
 },
 {
   "ID": 92,
   "Question": "Capital city of Laos?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Vientiane",
   "Answer1": "Vientiane",
   "Answer2": "Luanda",
   "Answer3": "Moscow"
 },
 {
   "ID": 93,
   "Question": "Capital city of Latvia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Riga",
   "Answer1": "Riga",
   "Answer2": "Yaren District (de facto)",
   "Answer3": "Lusaka"
 },
 {
   "ID": 94,
   "Question": "Capital city of Lebanon?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Beirut",
   "Answer1": "Beirut",
   "Answer2": "Mexico City",
   "Answer3": "Luxembourg "
 },
 {
   "ID": 95,
   "Question": "Capital city of Lesotho?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Maseru",
   "Answer1": "Madrid",
   "Answer2": "Djibouti ",
   "Answer3": "Maseru"
 },
 {
   "ID": 96,
   "Question": "Capital city of Liberia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Monrovia",
   "Answer1": "Majuro",
   "Answer2": "Bamako",
   "Answer3": "Monrovia"
 },
 {
   "ID": 97,
   "Question": "Capital city of Libya?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Tripoli",
   "Answer1": "Paramaribo",
   "Answer2": "Malabo (de jure), ",
   "Answer3": "Tripoli"
 },
 {
   "ID": 98,
   "Question": "Capital city of Liechtenstein?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Vaduz",
   "Answer1": "Male",
   "Answer2": "Vaduz",
   "Answer3": "Dili"
 },
 {
   "ID": 99,
   "Question": "Capital city of Lithuania?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Vilnius",
   "Answer1": "Dublin",
   "Answer2": "Vilnius",
   "Answer3": "Managua"
 },
 {
   "ID": 100,
   "Question": "Capital city of Luxembourg?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Luxembourg ",
   "Answer1": "N'Djamena",
   "Answer2": "Manama",
   "Answer3": "Luxembourg "
 },
 {
   "ID": 101,
   "Question": "Capital city of Macedonia (FYROM)?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Skopje",
   "Answer1": "Skopje",
   "Answer2": "Manila",
   "Answer3": "Tripoli"
 },
 {
   "ID": 102,
   "Question": "Capital city of Madagascar?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Antananarivo",
   "Answer1": "Antananarivo",
   "Answer2": "Maputo",
   "Answer3": "Panama City"
 },
 {
   "ID": 103,
   "Question": "Capital city of Malawi?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Lilongwe",
   "Answer1": "Harare",
   "Answer2": "Maseru",
   "Answer3": "Lilongwe"
 },
 {
   "ID": 104,
   "Question": "Capital city of Malaysia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Kuala Lumpur",
   "Answer1": "Mbabane (administrative)",
   "Answer2": "Reykjavik",
   "Answer3": "Kuala Lumpur"
 },
 {
   "ID": 105,
   "Question": "Capital city of Maldives?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Male",
   "Answer1": "Male",
   "Answer2": "Porto-Novo",
   "Answer3": "Mexico City"
 },
 {
   "ID": 106,
   "Question": "Capital city of Mali?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Bamako",
   "Answer1": "Bamako",
   "Answer2": "Helsinki",
   "Answer3": "Minsk"
 },
 {
   "ID": 107,
   "Question": "Capital city of Malta?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Valletta",
   "Answer1": "Mogadishu",
   "Answer2": "Valletta",
   "Answer3": "Vaduz"
 },
 {
   "ID": 108,
   "Question": "Capital city of Marshall Islands?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Majuro",
   "Answer1": "Bangkok",
   "Answer2": "Majuro",
   "Answer3": "Monaco"
 },
 {
   "ID": 109,
   "Question": "Capital city of Mauritania?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Nouakchott",
   "Answer1": "Majuro",
   "Answer2": "Monrovia",
   "Answer3": "Nouakchott"
 },
 {
   "ID": 110,
   "Question": "Capital city of Mauritius?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Port Louis",
   "Answer1": "Montevideo",
   "Answer2": "Port Louis",
   "Answer3": "Santiago"
 },
 {
   "ID": 111,
   "Question": "Capital city of Mexico?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Mexico City",
   "Answer1": "Brazzaville",
   "Answer2": "Mexico City",
   "Answer3": "Moroni"
 },
 {
   "ID": 112,
   "Question": "Capital city of Micronesia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Palikir",
   "Answer1": "Palikir",
   "Answer2": "Moscow",
   "Answer3": "Luanda"
 },
 {
   "ID": 113,
   "Question": "Capital city of Moldova?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Chisinau",
   "Answer1": "Muscat",
   "Answer2": "Chisinau",
   "Answer3": "Warsaw"
 },
 {
   "ID": 114,
   "Question": "Capital city of Monaco?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Monaco",
   "Answer1": "Nairobi",
   "Answer2": "Dhaka",
   "Answer3": "Monaco"
 },
 {
   "ID": 115,
   "Question": "Capital city of Mongolia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Ulaanbaatar",
   "Answer1": "Nassau",
   "Answer2": "Ulaanbaatar",
   "Answer3": "Chisinau"
 },
 {
   "ID": 116,
   "Question": "Capital city of Montenegro?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Podgorica",
   "Answer1": "Port Louis",
   "Answer2": "Naypyidaw",
   "Answer3": "Podgorica"
 },
 {
   "ID": 117,
   "Question": "Capital city of Morocco?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Rabat",
   "Answer1": "Kigali",
   "Answer2": "N'Djamena",
   "Answer3": "Rabat"
 },
 {
   "ID": 118,
   "Question": "Capital city of Mozambique?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Maputo",
   "Answer1": "New Delhi",
   "Answer2": "Maputo",
   "Answer3": "Funafuti"
 },
 {
   "ID": 119,
   "Question": "Capital city of Myanmar (Burma)?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Naypyidaw",
   "Answer1": "Ngerulmud",
   "Answer2": "Bangui",
   "Answer3": "Naypyidaw"
 },
 {
   "ID": 120,
   "Question": "Capital city of Namibia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Windhoek",
   "Answer1": "Caracas",
   "Answer2": "Niamey",
   "Answer3": "Windhoek"
 },
 {
   "ID": 121,
   "Question": "Capital city of Nauru?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Yaren District (de facto)",
   "Answer1": "Yaren District (de facto)",
   "Answer2": "Nicosia",
   "Answer3": "Seoul"
 },
 {
   "ID": 122,
   "Question": "Capital city of Nepal?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Kathmandu",
   "Answer1": "Manama",
   "Answer2": "Nouakchott",
   "Answer3": "Kathmandu"
 },
 {
   "ID": 123,
   "Question": "Capital city of Netherlands?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Amsterdam",
   "Answer1": "Hanoi",
   "Answer2": "Amsterdam",
   "Answer3": "Nukuʻalofa"
 },
 {
   "ID": 124,
   "Question": "Capital city of New Zealand?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Wellington",
   "Answer1": "Oslo",
   "Answer2": "Ashgabat",
   "Answer3": "Wellington"
 },
 {
   "ID": 125,
   "Question": "Capital city of Nicaragua?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Managua",
   "Answer1": "Islamabad",
   "Answer2": "Ottawa",
   "Answer3": "Managua"
 },
 {
   "ID": 126,
   "Question": "Capital city of Niger?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Niamey",
   "Answer1": "Honiara",
   "Answer2": "Niamey",
   "Answer3": "Ouagadougou"
 },
 {
   "ID": 127,
   "Question": "Capital city of Nigeria?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Abuja",
   "Answer1": "Abuja",
   "Answer2": "Managua",
   "Answer3": "Palikir"
 },
 {
   "ID": 128,
   "Question": "Capital city of North Korea?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Pyongyang",
   "Answer1": "Pyongyang",
   "Answer2": "Panama City",
   "Answer3": "Pretoria (administrative)"
 },
 {
   "ID": 129,
   "Question": "Capital city of Norway?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Oslo",
   "Answer1": "Paramaribo",
   "Answer2": "Palikir",
   "Answer3": "Oslo"
 },
 {
   "ID": 130,
   "Question": "Capital city of Oman?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Muscat",
   "Answer1": "Paris",
   "Answer2": "Jerusalem (East)",
   "Answer3": "Muscat"
 },
 {
   "ID": 131,
   "Question": "Capital city of Pakistan?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Islamabad",
   "Answer1": "Saint George's",
   "Answer2": "Phnom Penh",
   "Answer3": "Islamabad"
 },
 {
   "ID": 132,
   "Question": "Capital city of Palau?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Ngerulmud",
   "Answer1": "Monrovia",
   "Answer2": "Ngerulmud",
   "Answer3": "Podgorica"
 },
 {
   "ID": 133,
   "Question": "Capital city of Palestine?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Jerusalem (East)",
   "Answer1": "Port Louis",
   "Answer2": "Kyiv (Kiev)",
   "Answer3": "Jerusalem (East)"
 },
 {
   "ID": 134,
   "Question": "Capital city of Panama?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Panama City",
   "Answer1": "Port Moresby",
   "Answer2": "Bratislava",
   "Answer3": "Panama City"
 },
 {
   "ID": 135,
   "Question": "Capital city of Papua New Guinea?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Port Moresby",
   "Answer1": "Port Moresby",
   "Answer2": "Port of Spain",
   "Answer3": "Tarawa"
 },
 {
   "ID": 136,
   "Question": "Capital city of Paraguay?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Asunción",
   "Answer1": "Asunción",
   "Answer2": "Port Vila",
   "Answer3": "Jerusalem"
 },
 {
   "ID": 137,
   "Question": "Capital city of Peru?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Lima",
   "Answer1": "Lima",
   "Answer2": "Gaborone",
   "Answer3": "Port-au-Prince"
 },
 {
   "ID": 138,
   "Question": "Capital city of Philippines?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Manila",
   "Answer1": "Manila",
   "Answer2": "Malabo (de jure)",
   "Answer3": "Porto-Novo"
 },
 {
   "ID": 139,
   "Question": "Capital city of Poland?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Warsaw",
   "Answer1": "Prague",
   "Answer2": "Warsaw",
   "Answer3": "Algiers"
 },
 {
   "ID": 140,
   "Question": "Capital city of Portugal?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Lisbon",
   "Answer1": "Praia",
   "Answer2": "Lisbon",
   "Answer3": "Banjul"
 },
 {
   "ID": 141,
   "Question": "Capital city of Qatar?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Doha",
   "Answer1": "Kathmandu",
   "Answer2": "Doha",
   "Answer3": "Pretoria (administrative)"
 },
 {
   "ID": 142,
   "Question": "Capital city of Romania?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Bucharest",
   "Answer1": "Pristina",
   "Answer2": "Monaco",
   "Answer3": "Bucharest"
 },
 {
   "ID": 143,
   "Question": "Capital city of Russia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Moscow",
   "Answer1": "Bridgetown",
   "Answer2": "Moscow",
   "Answer3": "Pyongyang"
 },
 {
   "ID": 144,
   "Question": "Capital city of Rwanda?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Kigali",
   "Answer1": "Kigali",
   "Answer2": "Santo Domingo",
   "Answer3": "Quito"
 },
 {
   "ID": 145,
   "Question": "Capital city of Saint Kitts and Nevis?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Basseterre",
   "Answer1": "Basseterre",
   "Answer2": "Rabat",
   "Answer3": "Port Vila"
 },
 {
   "ID": 146,
   "Question": "Capital city of Saint Lucia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Castries",
   "Answer1": "Valletta",
   "Answer2": "Castries",
   "Answer3": "Reykjavik"
 },
 {
   "ID": 147,
   "Question": "Capital city of Saint Vincent and the Grenadines?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Kingstown",
   "Answer1": "Port-au-Prince",
   "Answer2": "Riga",
   "Answer3": "Kingstown"
 },
 {
   "ID": 148,
   "Question": "Capital city of Samoa?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Apia",
   "Answer1": "Sucre (de jure)",
   "Answer2": "Apia",
   "Answer3": "Riyadh"
 },
 {
   "ID": 149,
   "Question": "Capital city of San Marino?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "San Marino",
   "Answer1": "Zagreb",
   "Answer2": "Rome",
   "Answer3": "San Marino"
 },
 {
   "ID": 150,
   "Question": "Capital city of Sao Tome and Principe?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "São Tomé",
   "Answer1": "Tehran",
   "Answer2": "Roseau",
   "Answer3": "São Tomé"
 },
 {
   "ID": 151,
   "Question": "Capital city of Saudi Arabia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Riyadh",
   "Answer1": "Riyadh",
   "Answer2": "Sofia",
   "Answer3": "Saint George's"
 },
 {
   "ID": 152,
   "Question": "Capital city of Senegal?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Dakar",
   "Answer1": "Saint John's",
   "Answer2": "Dakar",
   "Answer3": "Nukuʻalofa"
 },
 {
   "ID": 153,
   "Question": "Capital city of Serbia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Belgrade",
   "Answer1": "San Jose",
   "Answer2": "Niamey",
   "Answer3": "Belgrade"
 },
 {
   "ID": 154,
   "Question": "Capital city of Seychelles?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Victoria",
   "Answer1": "Tashkent",
   "Answer2": "San Marino",
   "Answer3": "Victoria"
 },
 {
   "ID": 155,
   "Question": "Capital city of Sierra Leone?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Freetown",
   "Answer1": "Belmopan",
   "Answer2": "San Salvador",
   "Answer3": "Freetown"
 },
 {
   "ID": 156,
   "Question": "Capital city of Singapore?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Singapore",
   "Answer1": "Kuala Lumpur",
   "Answer2": "Singapore",
   "Answer3": "Sana'a"
 },
 {
   "ID": 157,
   "Question": "Capital city of Slovakia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Bratislava",
   "Answer1": "Sri Jayawardenepura Kotte",
   "Answer2": "Bratislava",
   "Answer3": "Santiago"
 },
 {
   "ID": 158,
   "Question": "Capital city of Slovenia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Ljubljana",
   "Answer1": "Ouagadougou",
   "Answer2": "Ljubljana",
   "Answer3": "Santo Domingo"
 },
 {
   "ID": 159,
   "Question": "Capital city of Solomon Islands?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Honiara",
   "Answer1": "Beirut",
   "Answer2": "Honiara",
   "Answer3": "São Tomé"
 },
 {
   "ID": 160,
   "Question": "Capital city of Somalia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Mogadishu",
   "Answer1": "Sarajevo",
   "Answer2": "Mogadishu",
   "Answer3": "Lisbon"
 },
 {
   "ID": 161,
   "Question": "Capital city of South Africa?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Pretoria (administrative)",
   "Answer1": "Singapore",
   "Answer2": "Seoul",
   "Answer3": "Pretoria (administrative)"
 },
 {
   "ID": 162,
   "Question": "Capital city of South Korea?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Seoul",
   "Answer1": "Seoul",
   "Answer2": "Minsk",
   "Answer3": "Singapore"
 },
 {
   "ID": 163,
   "Question": "Capital city of South Sudan?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Juba",
   "Answer1": "Roseau",
   "Answer2": "Juba",
   "Answer3": "Skopje"
 },
 {
   "ID": 164,
   "Question": "Capital city of Spain?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Madrid",
   "Answer1": "Libreville",
   "Answer2": "Madrid",
   "Answer3": "Sri Jayawardenepura Kotte"
 },
 {
   "ID": 165,
   "Question": "Capital city of Sri Lanka?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Sri Jayawardenepura Kotte",
   "Answer1": "Sofia",
   "Answer2": "Lilongwe",
   "Answer3": "Sri Jayawardenepura Kotte"
 },
 {
   "ID": 166,
   "Question": "Capital city of Sudan?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Khartoum",
   "Answer1": "Khartoum",
   "Answer2": "Castries",
   "Answer3": "Stockholm"
 },
 {
   "ID": 167,
   "Question": "Capital city of Suriname?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Paramaribo",
   "Answer1": "Paramaribo",
   "Answer2": "Canberra",
   "Answer3": "Sucre (de jure)"
 },
 {
   "ID": 168,
   "Question": "Capital city of Swaziland?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Mbabane (administrative)",
   "Answer1": "San Marino",
   "Answer2": "Mbabane (administrative)",
   "Answer3": "Suva"
 },
 {
   "ID": 169,
   "Question": "Capital city of Sweden?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Stockholm",
   "Answer1": "Tirana",
   "Answer2": "Taipei",
   "Answer3": "Stockholm"
 },
 {
   "ID": 170,
   "Question": "Capital city of Switzerland?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Bern",
   "Answer1": "Bern",
   "Answer2": "Kingston",
   "Answer3": "Tallinn"
 },
 {
   "ID": 171,
   "Question": "Capital city of Syria?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Damascus",
   "Answer1": "Damascus",
   "Answer2": "Accra",
   "Answer3": "Tarawa"
 },
 {
   "ID": 172,
   "Question": "Capital city of Taiwan?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Taipei",
   "Answer1": "Taipei",
   "Answer2": "Baku",
   "Answer3": "Tashkent"
 },
 {
   "ID": 173,
   "Question": "Capital city of Tajikistan?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Dushanbe",
   "Answer1": "Tbilisi",
   "Answer2": "Tallinn",
   "Answer3": "Dushanbe"
 },
 {
   "ID": 174,
   "Question": "Capital city of Tanzania?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Dodoma",
   "Answer1": "Tegucigalpa",
   "Answer2": "Dodoma",
   "Answer3": "Riyadh"
 },
 {
   "ID": 175,
   "Question": "Capital city of Thailand?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Bangkok",
   "Answer1": "Bangkok",
   "Answer2": "Tehran",
   "Answer3": "Asunción"
 },
 {
   "ID": 176,
   "Question": "Capital city of Timor-Leste?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Dili",
   "Answer1": "Astana",
   "Answer2": "Thimphu",
   "Answer3": "Dili"
 },
 {
   "ID": 177,
   "Question": "Capital city of Togo?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Lomé",
   "Answer1": "Lomé",
   "Answer2": "Riga",
   "Answer3": "Tunis"
 },
 {
   "ID": 178,
   "Question": "Capital city of Tonga?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Nukuʻalofa",
   "Answer1": "Tokyo",
   "Answer2": "Bern",
   "Answer3": "Nukuʻalofa"
 },
 {
   "ID": 179,
   "Question": "Capital city of Trinidad and Tobago?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Port of Spain",
   "Answer1": "Tripoli",
   "Answer2": "Andorra la Vella",
   "Answer3": "Port of Spain"
 },
 {
   "ID": 180,
   "Question": "Capital city of Tunisia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Tunis",
   "Answer1": "Paris",
   "Answer2": "Tunis",
   "Answer3": "Tirana"
 },
 {
   "ID": 181,
   "Question": "Capital city of Turkey?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Ankara",
   "Answer1": "Ankara",
   "Answer2": "Ulaanbaatar",
   "Answer3": "La Paz (seat of government)"
 },
 {
   "ID": 182,
   "Question": "Capital city of Turkmenistan?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Ashgabat",
   "Answer1": "Vaduz",
   "Answer2": "Praia",
   "Answer3": "Ashgabat"
 },
 {
   "ID": 183,
   "Question": "Capital city of Tuvalu?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Funafuti",
   "Answer1": "Nairobi",
   "Answer2": "Funafuti",
   "Answer3": "Valletta"
 },
 {
   "ID": 184,
   "Question": "Capital city of Uganda?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Kampala",
   "Answer1": "Montevideo",
   "Answer2": "Vatican City",
   "Answer3": "Kampala"
 },
 {
   "ID": 185,
   "Question": "Capital city of Ukraine?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Kyiv (Kiev)",
   "Answer1": "San Salvador",
   "Answer2": "Victoria",
   "Answer3": "Kyiv (Kiev)"
 },
 {
   "ID": 186,
   "Question": "Capital city of United Arab Emirates?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Abu Dhabi",
   "Answer1": "Skopje",
   "Answer2": "Abu Dhabi",
   "Answer3": "Vienna"
 },
 {
   "ID": 187,
   "Question": "Capital city of United Kingdom?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "London",
   "Answer1": "Stockholm",
   "Answer2": "Vientiane",
   "Answer3": "London"
 },
 {
   "ID": 188,
   "Question": "Capital city of United States of America?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Washington, D.C.",
   "Answer1": "Washington, D.C.",
   "Answer2": "Tokyo",
   "Answer3": "Vilnius"
 },
 {
   "ID": 189,
   "Question": "Capital city of Uruguay?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Montevideo",
   "Answer1": "Warsaw",
   "Answer2": "Montevideo",
   "Answer3": "Phnom Penh"
 },
 {
   "ID": 190,
   "Question": "Capital city of Uzbekistan?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Tashkent",
   "Answer1": "Washington, D.C.",
   "Answer2": "Abuja",
   "Answer3": "Tashkent"
 },
 {
   "ID": 191,
   "Question": "Capital city of Vanuatu?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Port Vila",
   "Answer1": "Havana",
   "Answer2": "Port Vila",
   "Answer3": "Wellington"
 },
 {
   "ID": 192,
   "Question": "Capital city of Vatican City?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Vatican City",
   "Answer1": "Brussels",
   "Answer2": "Vatican City",
   "Answer3": "Windhoek"
 },
 {
   "ID": 193,
   "Question": "Capital city of Venezuela?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Caracas",
   "Answer1": "Caracas",
   "Answer2": "Yamoussoukro",
   "Answer3": "Sarajevo"
 },
 {
   "ID": 194,
   "Question": "Capital city of Vietnam?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Hanoi",
   "Answer1": "Lusaka",
   "Answer2": "Hanoi",
   "Answer3": "Yaounde"
 },
 {
   "ID": 195,
   "Question": "Capital city of Yemen?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Sana'a",
   "Answer1": "Yaren District (de facto)",
   "Answer2": "Quito",
   "Answer3": "Sana'a"
 },
 {
   "ID": 196,
   "Question": "Capital city of Zambia?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Lusaka",
   "Answer1": "Lusaka",
   "Answer2": "Washington, D.C.",
   "Answer3": "Yerevan"
 },
 {
   "ID": 197,
   "Question": "Capital city of Zimbabwe?",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Harare",
   "Answer1": "Thimphu",
   "Answer2": "Zagreb",
   "Answer3": "Harare"
 }
]
}